<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Plymouth's Best Real Estate Training</title>
    <description>Kerby &amp; Cristina Skurat, a top Real Estate Agent in Plymouth, shares his/her own internal real estate agent training for free. His/Her Real Estate Training, Tips and Advice will help you sell more homes in less time.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 14:44:12 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 14:44:12 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.7.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>ShortSalesWebinar-M&amp;Z</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/LTKovn_-Hmg?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below, I’ve included the links to the documents mentioned in this video:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Kerby+Skurat/Effective_Client_Representation_Short_Sale_Class.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EFFECTIVE CLIENT REPRESENTATION IN SHORT SALE TRANSACTIONS&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://vyralmarketing.s3.amazonaws.com/Kerby+Skurat/SS_guide.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;AGENT GUIDE TO SHORT SALES&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions, don’t hesitate to reach out to us. We are happy to assist you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 10:41:28 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/shortsaleswebinar-mz.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/shortsaleswebinar-mz.html</guid>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Here’s Why Virtual Listing and Buyers Consultations Work!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/N4d_71aHG4c?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many agents have been asking us what the most crucial things are we can do for our clients during this challenging time so they can still make a move. The good news is, we’ve been doing this for years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A great thing you can do for buyers is to make sure they’re comfortable with the virtual process. We’re doing virtual consultations, helping them understand the process, getting a home search set up, then doing either a virtual showing or walk-through. If they’re extremely interested in the home, then we’ll conduct a safe, in-person showing of the house with all health precautions in place.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Make sure they’re comfortable with the virtual process.%20http://localhost:4000/heres-why-virtual-listing-and-buyers-consultations-work.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Make sure they’re comfortable with the virtual process.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For sellers, we’re doing virtual consultations and walk-throughs of their property. We’re reviewing our marketing strategy to ensure their home stands out from the competition, and that we find the right buyers. &lt;strong&gt;We’re making sure this is an easy and safe experience for them.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to learn more about how we help our clients during this pandemic, or you have any questions, reach out to me via phone or email at cristina@kerbyandcristina.com. There are many more ways we’re helping our clients right now, and we would love to discuss them with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;
 &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 15:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/heres-why-virtual-listing-and-buyers-consultations-work.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/heres-why-virtual-listing-and-buyers-consultations-work.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How We're Marketing During COVID-19</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/4khkSkQpn6w?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How are we currently conducting our marketing to continue to bring in buyers and sellers? Lately, &lt;strong&gt;we’ve shifted away from a lot of mass media and are focusing on digital marketing.&lt;/strong&gt; We’re also retargeting old leads and trying to get them back to our website. That’s allowing them to have an agent to reach out to and connect with, get set up with a custom home search, view virtual tours, and more. We’re using these opportunities to convert them into clients with showing appointments or virtual buyer consultations. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All these things are giving us a competitive edge in this market. Since we have such an extensive and wonderful staff, we’re able to leverage that talent and expertise at a high level. Marketing correctly for the times and market you’re in can make a real difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about our marketing or real estate in general, please reach out to us via phone or email. We would love to help you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 15:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-were-marketing-during-covid-19.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-were-marketing-during-covid-19.html</guid>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Listing Presentation</category>
        
        <category>Reviews and Referrals</category>
        
        <category>Lead Generation</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Have an Overpriced Listing? Use This Script to Ask For a Price Reduction!</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/1sVOPF8js5I?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How do you get a seller to agree to a price reduction?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When we meet with sellers, we show them a circular pricing chart that you can see at 0:22 in the video above.&lt;/strong&gt; The target price, or bullseye, is where you want to be because that will generate the most exposure for your home, attract the most offers, and capture the highest sale price. The bullseye is surrounded by three outer rings, each one representing a different degree of mispricing: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;4% to 6% off: Showings but no offers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;6% to 12% off: Drive-bys only and a low number of showings&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;+12% off: Drive-bys only &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when you sit down with one of your sellers, show them this chart and explain to them that due to the market activity you’ve been observing, buyers’ response to their home, and conversations you’ve had with other agents, you believe their home is inside one of the mispriced rings. Then, advise them to allow you to make a market adjustment and reduce their home’s price. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=The target price, or bullseye, is where you want to be.%20http://localhost:4000/have-an-overpriced-listing-use-this-script-to-ask-for-a-price-reduction.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“The target price, or bullseye, is where you want to be.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It’s important to be specific when reducing the price.&lt;/strong&gt; Either give the seller a range to go by or name an exact number. There are two ways in which to give them clear direction. First, propose the reduction in writing and include all the market comps, research, and other data. Second, follow up with a phone call after your meeting, and make sure you schedule this call in advance. It usually helps them if they’ve had some time to think about what you discussed. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to talk more about this or any real estate topic, don’t hesitate to reach out to me. I’m here to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 15:26:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/have-an-overpriced-listing-use-this-script-to-ask-for-a-price-reduction.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/have-an-overpriced-listing-use-this-script-to-ask-for-a-price-reduction.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to Connect with Your Clients During COVID-19</title>
        <description>&lt;iframe width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/pLQYbpxOYwA?rel=0&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many real estate agents have been asking us lately how they can stay in front of their clients during this pandemic. Staying in your client’s minds will help your business progress during this strange time. Here are two great ways to stay connected:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1. Make calls.&lt;/strong&gt; Whether you use a phone or video calling platform, it’s necessary to stay in touch with your sphere of influence (friends and family who know you) and current and past clients. The more you stay in touch with those who already know how wonderful you are, the more referrals you’ll receive over time. An easy script is to simply say who you are and ask how they’re doing. State that the lockdown is really affecting us all, then ask how it’s specifically impacting them. &lt;br /&gt;​​​​&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/home/?status=Staying in your client’s minds will help your business progress during this strange time.%20http://localhost:4000/how-to-connect-with-your-clients-during-covid-19.html%20via%40&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; class=&quot;pullquote&quot;&gt;“Staying in your client’s minds will help your business progress during this strange time.”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2. Use your resources at a deeper level.&lt;/strong&gt; We’re using tools we’ve had for a while, but we’re extending them further. There’s a blog we love called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.keepingcurrentmatters.com/blog/&quot;&gt;Keeping Current Matters&lt;/a&gt;; you should check it out if you’re interested. They have free online resources, and we’ve used a ton of their intel to help buyers and sellers understand what’s happening in the market so they can make informed decisions about their home purchase or sale. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of things have been changing due to the coronavirus, but you can still help people buy or sell real estate while staying safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions about staying in touch with clients during COVID-19 or real estate in general, please call or email us. We look forward to helping you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/strategy-call/&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/img/cta-images/full-strategy-call.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Strategy Call&quot; class=&quot;full-post-cta&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 May 2020 15:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/how-to-connect-with-your-clients-during-covid-19.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/how-to-connect-with-your-clients-during-covid-19.html</guid>
        
        <category>Buyer Prospects</category>
        
        <category>Lead Conversion</category>
        
        <category>Transaction Management</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
